## **AKSHAY GORE**

420 Nord Avenue, Apt. #5, Chico, CA, 95926

Contact: 408-921-5838 | Email: akshaygore06@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/akshaygore

GitHub: https://github.com/akshaygore06



## Summary

Currently working as database management intern at Distributed Learning Technologies, CSU Chico. Have two years of work experience as a software engineer. Seeking summer internship in the field of Software Development or Quality and Assurance with the goal of full-time employment.

#### Education

• MS in Computer Science, California State University – Chico, CA (Aug 2014 – Dec 2016) GPA 3.5/4.0

BE in Computer Technology, University of Nagpur, India (Aug 2008 – Dec 2012):

### **GPA** 3.5/4.0

# Work experience

### Intern, Distributed Learning Technologies, CSU Chico, CA

Jan 2016 - Present

- Working on Oracle 11g and 12c, Oracle SQL Data Modeler and Oracle SQL Developer.
- Developed a SITE USAGE report generation system.
- Developed DDL statements to create tables and to populate the database.
- Created complex queries using multiple select and joins queries to generate the reports.
- Created Views and Schedulers.
- Working on the Google Analytics and Microsoft PowerBI to analyze the traffic on the Blackboard LEARN website.

### Software Engineer, Inboxmasters Systems Pvt. Ltd. - Pune, India

Dec 2012 - May 2014

- Worked on LAMP (Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP) Environment
- Responsibilities included design and development of Email Marketing Campaign, Requirement Analysis, data monitoring and tracking
- Designed and developed data queries to target the specific users and provide efficient email marketing campaign for clients
- Prepared data analysis listings and activity, performance and progress reports

### **Academic Projects**

### **Book Tracking System (Java, Oracle 11g)**

- Developed an online system for the Office of Accessible Technology and Services which manages alternative media transactions for disabled students
- Used HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JSP and JS in frontend development

## Gold Chase (C++)

- Developed a real time multiplayer game in C++ on Unix system
- · Independently developed code incorporating shared memory, semaphores and graphics rendering

#### Library Search Engine (Python/C++)

- Solely responsible for developing a Search Engine to search for all possible results from given catalog of films, videos, periodicals and books
- Implemented using Object Oriented Methodology

#### **Skills & Expertise**

Languages: C, C++, Python, SQL, PL/SQL, Java, Java Script, HTML, CSS, Android Development, JSP

**Technical expertise:** Google Test, RDBMS, Oracle SQL Data Modeler, GIT, Bootstrap, Eclipse IDE, Visual Studio, Amazon Web Services, L.A.M.P, Windows, Mac, Android Studio, Algorithms, Oracle XE Database, GDB, VIM

### **Courses**

Software Engineering | Distributed Systems | Advance Database Mgmt. Systems | Object-Oriented Programming | Algorithm and Data Structures | Mobile Application Dev. | Design and Analysis of Algo. | Operating Systems